<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">YarumalTour</string>
    <string name="slogan">La Sultana del Norte</string>
    <string name="hoteles">Hotels</string>
    <string name="demografia">Demography</string>
    <string name="cerca">About </string>
    <string name="regreso">...</string>
    <string name="tgranh">It offers: large and comfortable rooms with double or single bed with WI-FI service and cable TV.
 Restaurant service. Special Plans for your couple.</string>
    <string name="ugranh">20th av # 20th - 46. Tel: 8536065</string>
    <string name="amajari">Amajari Hotel</string>
    <string name="tamajari"><![CDATA[Comfortable rooms with private bath, hot water, cable TV and WI-FI.
 Restaurant service. Make your event.]]></string>
    <string name="uamajari">Park of Yarumal. Tel: 8538866 Y 8870866</string>
    <string name="club">Chorros Blancos Country Club</string>
    <string name="tclub"><![CDATA[The best place for recreation Northern Antioquia, with a wonderful climate,
 good green areas, games, wet areas, pools, rooms, areas for camping, ecological trail
and bar and restaurant.]]></string>
    <string name="uclub">Located on Chorros Blancos.
        Tel: 853  85 00. Mobile 320 698 7704  and 320 698 6484</string>
    <string name="casona">La Casona Pub</string>
    <string name="tcasona">Inn and Disco. We offer to you good enviroment with crossover music.
 We have national and international liquors. We have special gifs for your birthday.
  Live music Shows.   Karaoke and a lot of good things.</string>
    <string name="ucasona">19th av # 22th, corner. Tel: 8874500 - Yarumal</string>
    <string name="texas">Texas Bar</string>
    <string name="ttexas">We offer a friendly atmosphere for talks, with the best American ballads and
         rock classics. local and imported liquors, beers and shots. Events on special dates.</string>
    <string name="utexas">19th st # 19th -70, Yarumal</string>
    <string name="mison">Mi son coffee bar</string>
    <string name="tmison">A place for enjoying and sharing. You are here by a dream;
 because we are convinced that the meeting extends beyond music and liquor: My Son our refuge
 where the word is welcome, laughter, hug, known among friends, where good stories
 They remain in time and transformed into feeling, poetry and images that invite nostalgic ..</string>
    <string name="umison">19th st # 19th -15. Tel: 8536807</string>

    <string name="religion">Seminary and Basilica</string>
    <string name="treligion1"><![CDATA[Tour of three places of religious and historical importance for the city:
         A minor basilica of Our Lady of Mercy. It is located in the main park of Yarumal.
         Features beautiful architecture and diferententes paintings and sculptures of great value. There also are
          the remains of Epifanio Mejia, Antioquia hymn writer. Its altar is made of marble of different colors
          and weighs 12 tons. It is the main religious center of the town.]]></string>
    <string name="treligion2"><![CDATA[The Yarumal seminar for foreign missions. It was founded in 1927, there were
         mission missionaries to go to different places of Colombia and the world priests.
         It is an old architectural work with mud walls, clay tile roof, hardwood floors.
         Today, in place SENA works and the work presents great deterioration.]]></string>
    <string name="treligion3">Cristo Sacerdote seminary. It was founded in 1969. It is located in the lower part of the urban area, on the road  toward Medellin.
 It has chapels which have different artistic works. There is extensive natural areas.</string>

    <string name="aventura">Natural Adventure and Historic travels</string>
    <string name="taventura1">Spa Mallarino and stone bridge Visit: In  Mallarino,Angostura road,
 there are  natural pools over Santa Rita river and also there are hostels. You will be able enjoy a very good river travel.
 You can also camping. And if you love adventure! There is a very good place for hiking, its name is Puente Piedra. </string>
    <string name="taventura2">Boqueron is other beatiful place, this is located in Campamento road. There you will find a lot of water source and you could see Nechi river valley
In the lowest part of the mountain there is a monument to Chorros Blancos Independence  Combat, happened in 1820.</string>
    <string name="taventura3"><![CDATA[Finally, two more recommendations: Cedeno and El Cedro little towns offer a lot of water and wooded sources.
But if you do not want to travel, in the Morro Azul Mount, at the top of the town, you can enjoy a spectacular view of the  valley
 of  Nechi river. This is  both , an environment adventure and religious, there there  is a place known as La Cruz,
 place of Catholic ceremonies.]]></string>

    <string name="generalidades">Overview</string>

    <string name="tdemo1"><![CDATA[Yarumal is a town located in northern Antioquia (Colombia).
             It covers an area of 724km2. It is located at an altitude of 2353 above sea level, at a distance
             123km of Medellin. It has 46865 inhabitants, of which 30515 are located in the urban area.
             The gentile is Yarumaleños.]]></string>
    <string name="detalles">Urban area has 27 suburb and rural area has 52 village and 7 small town.
 Urban area has 2 public high schools and 2 privated; it also has 9 public elementary schools.
 Each little town there is a high school.  Yarumal has good public services and medical centers.</string>

    <string name="version">YarumalTour version 1.0. Date: 04/04/2016</string>
    <string name="autor">Developed By:  Jose Esau Bedoya Vergara. Engineering Deparment - University of Antioquia
            This app was developed for academic purposes. Pictures were token from the official site of the companies or from Facebook.</string>
    <string name="bares">Pubs and Discos</string>
    <string name="frase">Place of important people and history</string>
    <string name="granh">Great Hotel</string>
    <string name="simbolos">Symbols</string>
    <string name="sitios">Touristic places</string>
    <string name="corregimientos">Little Towns</string>
    <string name="cedeno">CEDEÑO</string><string name="tcedeno">Cedeno is located 40 km east of Yarumal, has school and high school, health center and a small village of 3000 inhabitants.
 They are dedicated to agriculture and mining. It has great natural landscapes and water sources.</string><string name="tllanos">Los Llanos is located 30 km from Yarumal on the road to Medellin. It has a school, health center and a small village of 5000 inhabitants.
 It is weather moor at an altitude of 2600 meters. There are large agricultural areas There you can see beautiful sunrises and sunsets.</string><string name="tochali">It is located 40 km from Yarumal. It is an area dedicated to agriculture and mining. There is a village of 2000 inhabitants. It has a cableway that connects the township of La Loma.
You can enjoy beautiful natural landscapes, abundant water sources.</string>
    <string name="inicio">Home</string>
    <string name="maventura">Adventure</string>
    <string name="mreligion">Religion</string>
    <string name="rural">Country</string>


</resources>